# João Amaral

**Date of birth:** 01/03/1993 **Nationality:** Portuguese

**Gender:** Male

### **CONTACT**

Bairro do Bailador nº5 7580-199 Alcácer Do Sal, Portugal (Home)

🤝 joaomramaral42@gmail.com

(+351) 918313133

https://jamaral42.github.io/ portfolio/

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ joão-amaral-92614030b/



#### **ABOUT ME**

Bachelor's degree in Electronic, Telecommunications, and Computer Engineering from ISEL.

7 years at Mobileum (formerly WeDo Technologies) as a consultant in the telecommunications sector.

Programming foundations from university and now self-taught with a focus on web development.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

01/05/2020 - 07/01/2024 Lisboa, Portugal

Telecoms analysts Mobileum

Development of RAID systems (low-code software created by WeDo Technologies) in the telecommunications sector. Various projects related to telecommunications, mostly focused on commissions and revenue assurance.

01/02/2018 - 30/04/2020 Lisboa, Portugal

ICT advisor iCreate

## **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

**01/10/2011 - 01/10/2018** Lisboa, Portugal

Bachelor's degree in Electronic, Telecommunications, and Computer Engineering. Instituto Superior de Engenharia de Lisboa

Website <a href="https://www.isel.pt/">https://www.isel.pt/</a> | Level in EQF EQF level 6

The Complete 2024 Web Development Bootcamp Udemy

**Website** <a href="https://www.udemy.com/course/the-complete-web-development-bootcamp/">https://www.udemy.com/course/the-complete-web-development-bootcamp/</a>

**100 Days of Code: The Complete Python Pro Bootcamp** Ude my

Website https://www.udemy.com/course/100-days-of-code/

#### LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Portuguese

Other language(s):

**English** 

Listening C1Spoken production C1Reading C1Spoken interaction C1

Writing B2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

#### **DRIVING LICENCE**

•

**Driving Licence:** B